A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, National Commission on Water Quality, Series 9 FA379
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Donna Mitchell Reports (Cr-He), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 737)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (Hi-P), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 738)
- Donna Mitchell Reports (R-Z), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 739)
- Donna Mitchell Reports - History of Water Pollution Control (Late 19th Century to 1956) by Paul Eastman (Box 22, Folder 740)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1959-1964 (Box 22, Folder 741)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1965 (NAR testimony February 23, 1965 and May 19, 1965) (Box 22, Folder 742)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1966 Acts (Box 22, Folder 743)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1967 (NAR testimony April 26, 1967) (Box 22, Folder 744)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1968 (NAR testimony April 10, 1968, April 24, 1968) (Box 23, Folder 745)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 746)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Sewer and Water Programs, Farmers Home Administration, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 747)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Sewer and Water Programs, HUD, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 748)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Federal Water Quality Act Status Report, June 1970 (Box 23, Folder 749)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Federal Water Quality Act Construction Grants, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 750)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Bond Financing, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 751)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Manpower, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 752)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Mercury, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 753)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Amendments to Federal Water Pollution Control Act, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 754)
  Principally relating to oil discharge
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Legislation Introduced (Administration and Muskie Bills) (Box 23, Folder 755)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Needs Survey of National League of Cities, U.S. Conference of Mayors, July 1970 (Box 23, Folder 756)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Fiscal Year 1971 Appropriations for Environmental Programs (Box 23, Folder 757)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Pre-Financing Statistics, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 758)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State Projects - Status of Individual Projects on Pre-financing / Reimbursement, late 1970 (Box 23, Folder 759)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Pre-Financing Statistics, 50 States and Territories, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 760)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State Pre-Financing (1970 data) by Individual County (Box 23, Folder 761)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Rockefeller Testimony - Prepared Statements, 1965-1971 (Box 23, Folder 762)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Bond Issue ($1 billion), 1965 (Box 23, Folder 763)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State's Pure Waters Program, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 764)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Environment: New York State Laws on Water Pollution Control Through 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 765)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Counties & Towns, New York State (Box 23, Folder 766)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Status Reports - Construction Grant Program, August-November 1968 (Box 23, Folder 767)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - State: 5-Year Needs (Submitted July 1970 to FWQA) (Box 23, Folder 768)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Status Report, April 30, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 769)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - State Status Report (Approved Projects), June 30, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 770)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - State: Pending Projects as of June 30, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 771)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - State Status Report (Approved Projects), July 31, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 772)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - State Status Report (Approved Projects), August 31, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 773)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status of Pending Projects, September 30, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 774)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status of Inactive Projects (Completed or Cancelled Projects) Semi-Annual, September 15, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 775)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - State Status Report (Approved Projects) Quarterly, September 30, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 776)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - State Status Report (Approved Projects), September 30, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 777)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Report - Approved, March 31, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 778)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Report - Pending, March 31, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 779)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Report - Inactive, March 31, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 780)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Report - New York City, March 31, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 781)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Report, Pre-Financing, March 31, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 782)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York: Status Reports, June 30, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 783)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - State Status Report (Approved Projects), November 30, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 784)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Report (Pre-Financing), September 30, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 785)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Reports, December 31, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 786)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Reports, March 31, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 787)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Status Reports, June 30, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 788)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Status Reports, September 30, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 789)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Status Report (Approved & Inactive), September 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 790)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Status Report (Approved & Inactive), March 31, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 791)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Status Reports, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 792)
  PL660 - March 1976, PL92-500 - June 1976
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Problems (Other than New York) (Box 24, Folder 793)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Problems (Other than New York), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 794)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Problems (Other than New York), 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 795)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1970 Clean Air Act (PL91-604, December 31, 1970) (Box 24, Folder 796)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - President's Message on Environment, and Administration Bills, S-1012-1016 (Box 24, Folder 797)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1971 Appropriations, FY '72 (Box 24, Folder 798)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State (General) (Box 24, Folder 799)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Water Quality Classification & Standards Enforcement, 1971-72 (Box 24, Folder 800)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State - Monitoring & Surveillance (Box 24, Folder 801)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State - Air Pollution (Box 24, Folder 802)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House and Senate Public Works Committee Members (Box 24, Folder 803)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1971 Muskie Bill (S.523), February 2, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 804)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Analysis of Muskie and Administration Bills, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 805)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Diamond Statement to Muskie, April 12, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 806)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Legislation (Other Than Muskie & Administration), April 12, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 807)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - D. Mitchell Meeting with Albany DEC Directors, May 1971 (Box 24, Folder 808)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Rockefeller Letter to Governors, Muskie, and Blatnik (Reimbursement) (Box 24, Folder 809)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State Briefing of Congressional Delegation, June 8, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 810)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - The New Muskie Bill (with Staff Prints 1 & 2), May-June 1971 (Box 24, Folder 811)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State: Projects Submitted / Controversy re EPA 10% Grant Increases (HUD) (Box 24, Folder 812)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Loans In Lieu of State Matching Grants (to Qualify for 50/55% Federal Funding) (Box 24, Folder 813)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Costs for 1970 (S. Doc. 92-23); NGC Survey; House Survey (Box 25, Folder 814)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Public Works Committee Hearings, May-July 1971 (Box 25, Folder 815)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State Testimony Before House Public Works - R. Pedersen, DEC (Box 25, Folder 816)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate Committee Print #1 (Box 25, Folder 817)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Rockefeller Testimony Before House Public Works, July 28, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 818)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Muskie Subcommittee on Air and Water Pollution (Box 25, Folder 819)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate Committee Print #2, August 5, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 820)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senator Buckley Helicopter Trip Over New York State Projects (Box 25, Folder 821)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - EPA "One-Up-Manship" Over States, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 822)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - EPA Meeting with States, September 7, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 823)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Diamond Letter to Congressional Delegation September 17, 1971 and Eastman Letter to States September 2, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 824)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate Committee Print #2, October 8, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 825)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - New York State - Pending Projects: One-Year; Five-Year; Ten-Year (Box 25, Folder 826)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate Committee Print #3, October 27, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 827)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Views on Muskie Bill, September-October 1971 (Box 25, Folder 828)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate Report on S.2770 (Box 25, Folder 829)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate Passed S.2770 86-0, November 2, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 830)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Meeting in Boston and with Staff of Public Works Committee (Box 25, Folder 831)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Administration Proposed Amendments to S.2770 (Box 25, Folder 832)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1971 Senate Bill - Outside Comments on, November, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 833)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1971 Senate Bill - States' Comments on (as made to House Public Works Committee), November 19, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 834)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1971 Senate Bill - Scientists' Report on, December, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 835)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1971 Senate Bill - NAR Speech, November, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 836)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1971 Senate Bill - NAR to VP Agnew on Federal-State Relationships (Box 25, Folder 837)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - 1971 Senate Bill - Developments, November, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 838)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Committee and Staff Members Roster (Public Works) (Box 25, Folder 839)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill Introduced (H.R. 11896), November 19, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 840)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate and House Bills: Comparison (Box 25, Folder 841)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill: States' Comments on (Made to House Public Works), December 6, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 842)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Hearings (General), December 7-10, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 843)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Hearings Testimony (Adm. and Outside), December 7-10, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 844)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Hearings: Costs of Senate Bill (Estimate November 1, 1971 by Council of Economic Advisors) (Box 25, Folder 845)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Hearings: Costs of Senate Bill (New York State Estimates, December 7-10) (Box 25, Folder 846)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Hearings: NAR Testimony December 9 (Draft Testimony December 7-10) (Box 25, Folder 847)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Hearings: NAR Testimony December 9 and Letter to House Public Works Committee Following Testimony, December 7-10, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 848)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill, EPA Comments on H.R. 11896, December 13, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 849)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill, Reported December 15, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 850)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill: Definition of Pollution (Box 25, Folder 851)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate & House Bills: Attitudes Toward (Box 25, Folder 852)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Senate/House Bills: Status Reports End of 1971 (Box 25, Folder 853)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - President's Message on Environment, February 1972 (Box 25, Folder 854)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Conservation Foundation: Environment Forum, January 1972 (Box 25, Folder 855)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - National Governors' Conference (Governors' Coordinators Meeting) (Box 26, Folder 856)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - National Governors' Conference, Winter Meeting (February) (Box 26, Folder 857)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Appropriations, FY '73 (Ad Hoc Committee Testimony on Construction Grants & Reimbursements), 1973 (Box 26, Folder 858)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Developments (Overall), January-February 1972 (Box 26, Folder 859)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee - Denver Meeting, March 2-3, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 860)
  Position on legislation
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Committee Bill & Report (and Comparison with Senate and Administration Bills), March 1972 (Box 26, Folder 861)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill: NAR Telegram to New York Congressional Delegation (Box 26, Folder 862)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - EPA Symposium - State Environmental Legislation (Box 26, Folder 863)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee: Position on Legislation, March 15, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 864)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee: Position on Legislation, March 22-23, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 865)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill, Passage (Developments), March-April 1972 (Box 26, Folder 866)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill, Passage March 29, 1972 - Debate and News Clips (Box 26, Folder 867)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - House Bill - Contract Authority, March-May 1972 (Box 26, Folder 868)
- Cross Reference - Comparative Print, House/Senate Bills - Used by Conferees, Title I-Title III (Box 26, Folder 869)
  General note
  See Box 56.
- Cross Reference - Comparative Print, House/Senate Bills - Used by Conferees, Titles IV, V (Box 26, Folder 870)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Developments (Overall), March-October 1972 (Box 26, Folder 871)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee - Positions on Senate/House Bills, April 1972 (Box 26, Folder 872)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - April Meetings with EPA and States: Water Pollution Control Federation, National Wildlife Federation (Box 26, Folder 873)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee - Positions on Legislation, May 1972 (Box 26, Folder 874)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee - Positions on Legislation - Sent to (Box 26, Folder 875)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - "Sports Illustrated" Editorial, April & May, on Donna Mitchell and Henry Diamond (Box 26, Folder 876)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - National Governors' Conference, Houston (State Ad Hoc Committee), June 1-5, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 877)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Southern Water Resources Conference, May 1971 and June 1972 (Box 26, Folder 878)
  Positions on legislation
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Western States Water Council: Position on Legislation (Box 26, Folder 879)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee: Meetings on Legislation, and with Environmentalists, July 1972 (Box 26, Folder 880)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee: Meetings on Legislation, August 1972 (Box 26, Folder 881)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - States' Ad Hoc Committee: Meetings in Saint Louis, September 1972 (Box 26, Folder 882)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - D. Mitchell Memo and Meetings with T. N. Hurd, Secretary to Governor, September 1972 (Box 26, Folder 883)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Conference Committee - Development & Report of September 28, 1972 (House-Senate Passage in October) (Box 26, Folder 884)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Appropriations: Shortchanging 32 States (Box 26, Folder 885)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Veto and Override (Box 26, Folder 886)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Developments (Overall) (Box 26, Folder 887)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Book: History of Development of Public Law 92-500 (Box 26, Folder 888)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Lieber, Prof. Harvey (Box 26, Folder 889)
- Water Pollution (Federal Activities) - Lieber - Vouchers (Box 26, Folder 890)
- Cross Reference - Professor Harvey Lieber's Book - "Federalism and Clean Water" (Box 26, Folder 891)
  Table of Contents through Chapter 3
- Cross Reference - Professor Harvey Lieber's Book - "Federalism and Clean Water" (Box 26, Folder 892)
  Chapter 4 through Conclusion
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters/Memoranda, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 893)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters/Memoranda, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 894)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters/Memoranda, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 895)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters/Memoranda, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 896)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR and Muskie - Letters to (Box 27, Folder 897)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters re Budget of NCWQ (Box 27, Folder 898)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Delegations of Authority, May 1973 - July 1976 (Box 27, Folder 899)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters re National Academy of Sciences' Review of Staff Draft and Final Report to Commission (Box 27, Folder 900)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters to Top Staff, Fall 1975 (Box 27, Folder 901)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR and Environmentalists: Letters to, and to Commissioners (Box 27, Folder 902)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters/Memoranda: Atlanta Meeting, July 9, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 903)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Picnic for Staff - Invitation, July 1975 (Box 27, Folder 904)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters/Memoranda - Meetings Outside Groups, July-November 1975 (Box 27, Folder 905)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR to Outside Groups on First Staff Draft Report, September 1975 (Box 27, Folder 906)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters to Outside Groups re Staff Draft Report and January Hearings, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 907)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR and Other Commissioners' Statements at January 1976 Hearings (Box 27, Folder 908)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters/Memoranda on January 1976 Commission Hearings (Box 27, Folder 909)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - NAR Letters: Thanks to Commissioners, Staff and Consultants, March-April 1975 (Box 27, Folder 910)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Mitchell (Donna) Memoranda to States (Beginning September 1971) (Box 27, Folder 911)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Mitchell (Donna) Memoranda to States (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 912)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Mitchell (Donna) Memoranda to States (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 913)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Mitchell (Donna) Memoranda to States, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 914)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - President's Message (Environment), February 19 and September 10, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 915)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Budget, EPA, FY '74, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 916)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Appropriations, EPA, FY '74, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 917)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Budgets, EPA, FY '75, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 918)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Appropriations, EPA, FY '75, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 919)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Budget Reform Act of 1974 (PL93-344) (Box 27, Folder 920)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Budget, EPA, FY '76, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 921)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Appropriations, EPA, FY '76, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 922)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Budget, EPA, FY '77, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 923)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Appropriations, EPA, FY '77, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 924)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation: Water Quality Strategy Paper, 1st Edition, January 1973 (Box 27, Folder 925)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation: Water Quality Strategy Paper, 2nd Edition, March 1974 (Box 27, Folder 926)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation: Water Quality Strategy Paper, 3rd Edition, FY '76, 4th Edition, FY '77, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 927)
- NOT USED (Box 27, Folder 928)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation (Overall) (Box 27, Folder 929)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation: TAGs - Technical Advisory Group (Roster) (Box 27, Folder 930)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation: PIGs - Public Interest Groups, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 931)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation: Mitch Wendell Briefing of Albany (Box 27, Folder 932)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - EPA Flow Chart (Timetable) and Status Reports, November 1972 - May 1973 (Box 27, Folder 933)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation - State Task Groups (Proposed), January-February 1973 (Box 27, Folder 934)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation - Committee of Ten - Original Organization (Box 27, Folder 935)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation - State Committee of Ten, Formal Establishment, June 27, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 936)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation - 1972 Amendments to the Federal Water Pollution Control Act, November 20, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 937)
- NAR Chronological Correspondence - Implementation - State Committee of Ten Meetings, 1973-1976 (Box 27, Folder 938)
- Construction Grants - Tables, June 1975 (Box 27, Folder 939)
- Construction Grants - Reallocation of FY '71 Funds (to Atlanta, Cleveland, and Detroit), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 940)
  Also: EPA Discretionary Authority
- Construction Grants - Allocation of FY '71 and FY '72 Funds, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 941)
- Construction Grants - State Programs, FY 72, Amendments to Law to Authorize Extensions for FY '72, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 942)
- Construction Grants - Senate/House Bills - Allocations to New York State (Box 28, Folder 943)